<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>welcome on Яeversed Ƨiddhartha</title>
    <link>https://ahtrahddis.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in welcome on Яeversed Ƨiddhartha</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyleft 2020, ahtrahddis.</copyright><atom:link href="https://ahtrahddis.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>changelog</title>
      <link>https://ahtrahddis.github.io/changelog/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ahtrahddis.github.io/changelog/</guid>
      <description> Changelog 2020-10-05   replaced text font with IBM Plex Mono (commit) - reverted to old (Verdana) font for the website title (commit)
  added John Vervaeke&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;Awakening from the Meaning of Crisis&amp;rdquo; link (commit)****
  2020-09-30  changed URL from atrahhdis.github.io to ahtrahddis.github.io renamed website to &amp;ldquo;Reversed Siddhartha&amp;rdquo; changed to &amp;ldquo;hugo bear blog&amp;rdquo; theme added &amp;ldquo;A non-mystical explanation of insight meditation and the three characteristics of existence&amp;rdquo;  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>dharma</title>
      <link>https://ahtrahddis.github.io/dharma/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ahtrahddis.github.io/dharma/</guid>
      <description>Practice How do I start meditating? Below you will find a link to a compressed file that includes instructions in pdf format for the following techniques:
  Mindfulness of Breath (from TMI)
  Mahasi Vipassana (Noting) (from this blog)
  Shikantaza (Zazen) (from this e-book)
  Do nothing from (from Shinzen&amp;rsquo;s Five ways to know yourself and &amp;ldquo;Do Nothing&amp;rdquo; Meditation youtube video)
  Metta (Loving Kindness) from (this post)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>e-book creation how-to</title>
      <link>https://ahtrahddis.github.io/e-book-how-to/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ahtrahddis.github.io/e-book-how-to/</guid>
      <description>E-book Creation For the creation of all these e-books, the following procedure is followed:
  the text is pasted &amp;amp; formatted with / written in / converted to markdown (the conversion is done using various methods) - in rare cases other formats, ie. html, are used
  the markdown (.md) file is converted to epub using pandoc
  the epub file is edited with calibre and finally&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>info</title>
      <link>https://ahtrahddis.github.io/info/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ahtrahddis.github.io/info/</guid>
      <description>Contact If you want to contact me, please send me an email:
ns |at| mahasivipassana |dot| com.
If you found a typo or formatting issue or&amp;hellip;. on an e-book, apart from sending me an email, you can create a github account, fork the relevant repository, apply any change you suggest and then push it back to me.
 Changelog In order to see website changes, new addiditons etc., visit this link.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pragmatic dharma</title>
      <link>https://ahtrahddis.github.io/pragmatic-dharma/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ahtrahddis.github.io/pragmatic-dharma/</guid>
      <description>What is Pragmatic Dharma?   What is Pragmatic Dharma? by Ron Crouch
  The Core Features of Pragmatic Dharma by Vince Horn
  In case you didn&amp;rsquo;t notice it, there&amp;rsquo;s a dedicated subsection with various Pragmatic Dharma texts on the main page of this website.
 What about the &amp;ldquo;mushroom culture&amp;rdquo;? Here&amp;rsquo;s a short story shared by Kenneth Folk via his twitter account:
 &amp;hellip;..In fact, Bill (editor&amp;rsquo;s note: Hamilton) was himself an unabashed mushroomer, and not only withheld information but advocated doing so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Core Features of Pragmatic Dharma</title>
      <link>https://ahtrahddis.github.io/texts/pragmatic-dharma/the-core-features-of-pragmatic-dharma/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ahtrahddis.github.io/texts/pragmatic-dharma/the-core-features-of-pragmatic-dharma/</guid>
      <description>This is an article by Vince Horn.
 Introduction Pragmatic Dharma is a contemporary approach to awakening, rooted in tradition. It pulls from the time-tested teachings and practices of the Buddhist tradition, but is simultaneously infused with a contemporary mindset that isn’t afraid to tinker with the traditional formulations.
Pragmatic Dharma, at its core, is about asking the question: What works? If something doesn’t work, then it’s relinquished. If it works, it’s used.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>useful links</title>
      <link>https://ahtrahddis.github.io/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ahtrahddis.github.io/links/</guid>
      <description>Useful Links  Teachers   Mahasi Sayadaw
  Sayadaw U Tejaniya
   Suttas   SuttaCentral
  Pali Audio
   Communities  r/streamentry (a practice oriented reddit community)   Online Books   Mindfulness in Plain English by Ven. Henepola Gunaratana
  Mastering the Core Teachings of the Buddha by Daniel Ingram
  Contemplative Fitness by Kenneth Folk
   Youtube   Doug&amp;rsquo;s Dharma (an amazing secular/early Buddhism resource)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Pragmatic Dharma?</title>
      <link>https://ahtrahddis.github.io/texts/pragmatic-dharma/what-is-pragmatic-dharma/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ahtrahddis.github.io/texts/pragmatic-dharma/what-is-pragmatic-dharma/</guid>
      <description>This is an article by Ron Crouch.
I’ve been thinking a lot about what “pragmatic dharma” is lately. This is partly because I’m trying to get my own head straight as I write about it, and partly because Jack Kornfield recently criticized it on Buddhist Geeks. Kornfield, in his usual gentle style, was mostly circumspect in his criticism, but he did say that the leaders of the pragmatic dharma movement (I’m assuming he means Kenneth Folk and Daniel Ingram) have redefined key concepts in Buddhism.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
