<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>welcome on Reversed Siddhartha</title>
    <link>https://ahtrahddis.eu/</link>
    <description>Recent content in welcome on Reversed Siddhartha</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyleft 2020, ahtrahddis.</copyright><atom:link href="https://ahtrahddis.eu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>dharma</title>
      <link>https://ahtrahddis.eu/dharma/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ahtrahddis.eu/dharma/</guid>
      <description>Dharma Practice Meditation instructions for beginners Here, you will get a compressed file that includes instructions in pdf for the following meditation techniques:
  Mindfulness of Breath (from TMI)
  Mahasi Vipassana (Noting) (from this blog)
  Shikantaza (Zazen) (from this e-book)
  Do nothing from (from Shinzen&amp;rsquo;s Five ways to know yourself and &amp;ldquo;Do Nothing&amp;rdquo; Meditation youtube video)
  Metta (Loving Kindness) (from this post)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>e-book creation how-to</title>
      <link>https://ahtrahddis.eu/e-book-how-to/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ahtrahddis.eu/e-book-how-to/</guid>
      <description>E-book Creation For the creation of all these e-books, the following procedure is followed:
  the text is pasted &amp;amp; formatted with / written in / converted to markdown (and very rarely to html)
  the markdown (.md) file is converted to epub using pandoc
  the epub file is edited with calibre and finally&amp;hellip;
  the epub file is converted to mobi and azw3 with calibre</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>info</title>
      <link>https://ahtrahddis.eu/info/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ahtrahddis.eu/info/</guid>
      <description>Info Who Am I? It really doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter at all who I am, but let me give you some context.
I&amp;rsquo;m a secular Buddhist and an amateur photographer.
I used to be a pragmatic Mahasi noting geek, obsessed with the Progress of Insight map, until I decided to stop chasing my tail.
My current practice is heavily influenced by:
  Sayadaw U Tejaniya
  Soto Zen (mainly Kōdō Sawaki and Gudo Wafu Nishijima lineages)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>pragmatic dharma</title>
      <link>https://ahtrahddis.eu/pragmatic-dharma/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ahtrahddis.eu/pragmatic-dharma/</guid>
      <description>What is Pragmatic Dharma?   What is Pragmatic Dharma? by Ron Crouch
  The Core Features of Pragmatic Dharma by Vince Horn
  In case you didn&amp;rsquo;t notice it, there&amp;rsquo;s a dedicated subsection with various Pragmatic Dharma texts on the main page of this website.
 What about the &amp;ldquo;mushroom culture&amp;rdquo;? Here&amp;rsquo;s a short story shared by Kenneth Folk via his twitter account:
 &amp;hellip;..In fact, Bill (editor&amp;rsquo;s note: Hamilton) was himself an unabashed mushroomer, and not only withheld information but advocated doing so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Core Features of Pragmatic Dharma</title>
      <link>https://ahtrahddis.eu/texts/pragmatic-dharma/the-core-features-of-pragmatic-dharma/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ahtrahddis.eu/texts/pragmatic-dharma/the-core-features-of-pragmatic-dharma/</guid>
      <description>The Core Features of Pragmatic Dharma This is an article by Vince Horn.
 Introduction Pragmatic Dharma is a contemporary approach to awakening, rooted in tradition. It pulls from the time-tested teachings and practices of the Buddhist tradition, but is simultaneously infused with a contemporary mindset that isn’t afraid to tinker with the traditional formulations.
Pragmatic Dharma, at its core, is about asking the question: What works? If something doesn’t work, then it’s relinquished.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>useful links</title>
      <link>https://ahtrahddis.eu/links/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ahtrahddis.eu/links/</guid>
      <description>Useful Links Early Buddhism   In the Buddha’s Words (open source edition)
  SuttaCentral
  Pali Audio
   Teachers   Sayadaw U Tejaniya
  Sheng Yen
  Loch Kelly
  Stephan Bodian
  Diana Winston
   Communities   r/streamentry
  r/awakeawareness
   Online Books  Mindfulness in Plain English by Ven. Henepola Gunaratana   Youtube  Doug&amp;rsquo;s Dharma (an amazing secular/early Buddhism resource)   Podcasts  Zen Studies   Various  Meditator-X (MettaJunkie&amp;rsquo;s blog)  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Pragmatic Dharma?</title>
      <link>https://ahtrahddis.eu/texts/pragmatic-dharma/what-is-pragmatic-dharma/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ahtrahddis.eu/texts/pragmatic-dharma/what-is-pragmatic-dharma/</guid>
      <description>What is Pragmatic Dharma? This is an article by Ron Crouch.
I’ve been thinking a lot about what “pragmatic dharma” is lately. This is partly because I’m trying to get my own head straight as I write about it, and partly because Jack Kornfield recently criticized it on Buddhist Geeks. Kornfield, in his usual gentle style, was mostly circumspect in his criticism, but he did say that the leaders of the pragmatic dharma movement (I’m assuming he means Kenneth Folk and Daniel Ingram) have redefined key concepts in Buddhism.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
