<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Texts on Reversed Siddhartha</title>
    <link>https://ahtrahddis.eu/texts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Texts on Reversed Siddhartha</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>Copyleft 2020, ahtrahddis.</copyright><atom:link href="https://ahtrahddis.eu/texts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Core Features of Pragmatic Dharma</title>
      <link>https://ahtrahddis.eu/texts/pragmatic-dharma/the-core-features-of-pragmatic-dharma/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ahtrahddis.eu/texts/pragmatic-dharma/the-core-features-of-pragmatic-dharma/</guid>
      <description>The Core Features of Pragmatic Dharma This is an article by Vince Horn.
 Introduction Pragmatic Dharma is a contemporary approach to awakening, rooted in tradition. It pulls from the time-tested teachings and practices of the Buddhist tradition, but is simultaneously infused with a contemporary mindset that isn’t afraid to tinker with the traditional formulations.
Pragmatic Dharma, at its core, is about asking the question: What works? If something doesn’t work, then it’s relinquished.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What is Pragmatic Dharma?</title>
      <link>https://ahtrahddis.eu/texts/pragmatic-dharma/what-is-pragmatic-dharma/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ahtrahddis.eu/texts/pragmatic-dharma/what-is-pragmatic-dharma/</guid>
      <description>What is Pragmatic Dharma? This is an article by Ron Crouch.
I’ve been thinking a lot about what “pragmatic dharma” is lately. This is partly because I’m trying to get my own head straight as I write about it, and partly because Jack Kornfield recently criticized it on Buddhist Geeks. Kornfield, in his usual gentle style, was mostly circumspect in his criticism, but he did say that the leaders of the pragmatic dharma movement (I’m assuming he means Kenneth Folk and Daniel Ingram) have redefined key concepts in Buddhism.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
